dailycomedy.com 2010-05-16

# DailyComedy.com | Privacy Policy

News Alert!  **Congrats to DailyComedy.com's[Bix Brillo](http://www.dailycomedy.com/u/BixBrillo), [Gary B.](http://www.dailycomedy.com/u/Gary226), and [Cara Tramontano](http://www.dailycomedy.com/u/theCara) for having their Toyota jokes (along with jokes by Letterman, Leno and Colbert) featured in [USA Today](http://content.usatoday.com/communities/driveon/post/2010/02/jokes/1)!**

## Daily Comedy Privacy Policy

Not Kidding

**DailyComedy.com Member/Fan Value Proposition**  
DailyComedy.com is a website on which several of America's funniest comedians post topical jokes in text and on video every day in their own, unique, funny, and often twisted style.

We created DailyComedy.com to make it easy to share jokes and information with your friends and other fans of comedy. We give you control of your information--you tell people only what you want them to know about you in your profile on your comedy stage. Also, DailyComedy.com believes you should have access only to the information others want to share.

**DailyComedy.com Privacy Policy**  
DailyComedy.com's privacy policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and to help you make informed decisions when using DailyComedy.com.

By using or accessing DailyComedy.com, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. Information We Gather when you visit DailyComedy.com, you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and website use information collected by us as you interact with DailyComedy.com.

When you register with DailyComedy.com, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your zip code, your gender, your birth date, and some preference information.

When you enter DailyComedy.com, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all DailyComedy.com visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to DailyComedy.com. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.

When you use DailyComedy.com, you may perform searches, set up a comedy stage, visit other comedy stages, interact with advertising, and transmit information by means of various types of functionality. We collect this information so that we can provide you DailyComedy.com's services and offer personalized features. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information, if necessary.

By using DailyComedy.com, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed worldwide.

**How DailyComedy.com Uses Information It Collects**  
When you register with DailyComedy.com, you create your own profile, privacy settings, and comment preferences. Your profile information (which you control), as well as your name and photo, are displayed on your comedy stage to enable other people to connect with you, and you choose other people who you want to be a fan of. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by DailyComedy.com, its subsidiaries and affiliates, which we think you may find valuable.

Profile information you submit to DailyComedy.com will be available to visitors to your comedy stage. Your name, your comedy stage name, and profile picture thumbnail will be available in search results on DailyComedy.com.

DailyComedy.com may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating how many people like another fan or a comedian and to personalizing advertisements and promotions so that we can provide relevant information to you.

**Sharing Information With Third Parties**  
We do not provide contact information to third parties without your permission. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is reasonably necessary to offer the service, legally required or permitted by you. For example: 

  * We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about DailyComedy.com, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. If we use third parties for the processing of any personal information, we will make reasonable efforts to implement contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to DailyComedy.com specified purposes.
  * We will not sell your email address to third parties or the DailyComedy.com list of email addresses to third parties.
  * We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the DailyComedy.com service or using the DailyComedy.com name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents, or government agencies.

**Third Party Advertising**  
Ads that appear on DailyComedy.com can be served directly to members/fans by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address in such cases. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and web beacons (also known as 1x1 gifs) to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Using these techniques allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an ad in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where you or individuals using your computer saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked on. DailyComedy.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on DailyComedy.com unless you choose to share it with them.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by DailyComedy.com and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

**Changing Or Removing Information**  
Access and control over personal information on DailyComedy.com is available through the comedy stage profile editing tools. DailyComedy.com users may modify or remove any of their profile information at any time by logging onto their account. Information will be updated immediately when changed. Individuals who wish to deactivate their DailyComedy.com account may do so. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to members of DailyComedy.com. You can also remove fans and comedians from your comedy stage by using the editing tools.

**Security**  
DailyComedy.com takes all commercially reasonable precautions to protect our member/fans' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you NOT send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions about the security of DailyComedy.com, please contact us at [editor@dailycomedy.com](mailto:editor@dailycomedy.com).
